Alright, in this video I will tell you about differences in pricing and how it can affect
the whole development process.
So I prefer most famous platforms, obviously there are more platforms but we have to look
for a variable, that are important.
And the most important thing is unlimited request because if you create application you
might need a lot of changes because AI is not perfect.
Also as you can see, the level is very popular, it has beautiful design, it's pretty simple
and no code.
As you can see, you can set up for free and get for example like 5 requests per day as far
as you remember.
But if you want to use like a pro, you will get on 100 monthly credits, so keep that
in mind.
You just get like personal projects, some training, some templates, but still it's 100
monthly credits.
So you are limited to this number and if you create maybe simple website, it might be
enough, but if you create like a Chrome extension or maybe web application, then you will
have a problem because many projects especially at once that you want to monetize will
require fixes, tweaks and there is no way you can make it within a few prums.
So as you can see, it's 100 monthly credits, great, we have a bold, bold is popular as well,
there is a free tier, we have a 1 million tokens per month and 300,000 tokens per day
they limit.
Okay, and now we have a per month, but it's still as you can see, there is no day to
can limit, that's actually great, it costs $25.
We have some upload limit, but still, yeah, we have this possibility of that request that
can be and this is actually great that if you don't use all of the tokens, you roll over
the next month.
In replet, there's another story, because as you can see, there's like a 20 per month,
full agent free access, but still $25 per monthly credits, so it's not clearly stated what
exactly is here, it just shows that yeah, you will get some of the amount of credits, but
how they are redistribute, how you can use it, maybe you will run all the credits, maybe
in a few days and then what they'll, you probably need to apply for like some enter pricing
or custom order, which is not suitable, especially if you are starting.
So now we have a view zero from Verso and there is obviously possibly to have $5 per
monthly credits and in premium, there's like a 20, so still not a lot, especially if you
have to pay $20, so we still have some sort of the tokens.
So many platforms have a hard usage corpus, credit stock and messages, or protocol
usage cost models, some platforms like Replet for example, combine futures like id+hosting,
but they still have the elements, now we have a cursor and wind serve, so this is like
an old code, they are like assistants, we've imbued editor, which actually is very great
and it's not very hard because you don't need to type code manually, you just have
probably different design really, so it should be scary out, as you can see cursor, it has
extended limits on agents, but unlimited tap concussions and this is Maximo, context, windows
and background engines, so this is usage on all, but if you go to a prom, you can
get more than information that actually is unlimited, so basically, only free has this
option, but after that we can get the still unlimited usage that will cover it, and here
we check, this is like for daily tap users, and this is pro for like daily agent users,
so if you create an agent maybe you might consider it, but we use prom, obviously you can
try to use all of these platforms and try to combine and just pass code, but it will not
be very effective, we have a wind serve, wind serve is very popular and quite good, but
this is the problem, we have only 500 progress per hour, it's still better than some
of the previous models, but there is a limit, and in prom, we have unlimited tap concussions
unlimited, so this is the most important because we can just, unlimited lane, fix up the
stuff, because you don't know how many prance you will need to finish your project and
then obviously, and then cover all the fixes, so let's compare five for popular, a coding
development system platforms, level will give you free tier, but then you pay for credits
or messages, right, bold, users like token base model, rapid offers free store to plan,
and then we have a core, and versatile, has like this 20 mile premium and higher tier
plans, but also all API usage price per token, and then we have a cursor, that offers
a very appealing propositions on the prop plan, you get unlimited tap concussions, background
agents and no fixed token cap listed, which means you don't have to constantly watch your
token budget, that said always check the fine part, unlimited may still mean you face slower
performance or hidden rate limits, under heavy load, but from many users, especially for
sell or developers, learners or cars builders, cursor model can deliver more freedom
than the more strictly quoted alternatives.